What dies here...stays here.
The Drowned is a horror, drama, thriller film directed by Bruce G. Hallenbeck.
Kate Williams inherits her grandmother's cottage on a remote lake.
There, she encounters apparitions that seem to emanate from a submerged church where a
congregation drowned over 100 years ago...but there is more than meets the eye.
Kate Williams, played by Stephanie Tanaka.
Edgar Van Dam, played by Nick Miscusi.
Colleen O'Hanlon, played by Helen Black.
Father Merrow, played by Jeff Kirkendall.
Changeling, played by Vincent De Paul.
Jenny Greenteeth, played by Susan Hallenbeck.
Casino Royale is a 2006 spy thriller film, the twenty-first in the James Bond series by Eon Productions, the third screen adaptation of
Ian Fleming's 1953 novel of the same name, and the first to star Daniel Craig as the fictional MI6 agent James Bond.
The second entry in the film series to be directed by Martin Campbell, its screenplay was written by Neal Purvis,
Robert Wade, and Paul Haggis, and co-stars Eva Green, Mads Mikkelsen, Judi Dench, and Jeffrey Wright.
In the film, Bond is on a mission to bankrupt the terrorism financier Le Chiffre
(Mikkelsen) in a high-stakes poker game at the Casino Royale in Montenegro.
Following Die Another Day (2002), Eon decided to reboot the franchise, attempting to provide a
realistic and darker exploration of a less experienced and more vulnerable Bond.
Casting involved a widespread search for a new actor to succeed Pierce Brosnan as Bond; the
choice of Craig, announced in October 2005, initially proved controversial.
Principal photography took place in the Bahamas, Italy, the United Kingdom, and the Czech Republic, with
interior sets built at Pinewood Studios and Barrandov Studios, from January to July 2006.
The film features primarily practical stuntwork as opposed to the
computer-generated placements seen in other Bond films.
Casino Royale premiered at the Odeon Leicester Square on 14 November 2006, and was theatrically
released first in the United Kingdom on 16 November, and in the United States a day later.
The film received critical acclaim, with praise for Craig's reinvention of the
character and the departure from the tropes of previous Bond films.
It grossed over $616 million worldwide, becoming the fourth highest-grossing film of 2006
and the highest-grossing James Bond film until the release of Skyfall (2012).
A sequel, Quantum of Solace, was released in 2008.
The film explores themes of insanity, water
monster, drowned, ghost, evil spirits.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.